<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Antonio&#39;s Technology</title>
    <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Antonio&#39;s Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Wordpress to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/migrating-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/migrating-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Migrating from Wordpress to Hugo When I first started my blog about a year ago I decided to use Wordpress since I had a bit of experience with it from using it when I was little, and I had a lot of fun setting it up in my OCI free instance and having to mess with the firewalls and security rules and Cloudflare SSL to make it work kind of ok, but after going a year without writing any blog posts I realized that I was blocked because the overhead of publishing in Wordpress just took out the fun of writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python program to restore my WiFi networks</title>
      <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/python-program-to-restore-my-wifi-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/python-program-to-restore-my-wifi-networks/</guid>
      <description>Python program to restore my WiFi networks I recently got a new phone and have been loving it so far. I wanted an amoled screen, stereo speakers and 120Hz screen refresh rate since most of what I do on my phone is watching videos.
I use Android because I like playing around with my phone by rooting it and installing custom ROMs and whatever. Every time I switched roms it was like getting a new phone so I had to do all the configurations from the beginning, but I liked that all my WiFi networks transfered automatically using the google backup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Pi-Hole with a recursive DNS Server</title>
      <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/setting-up-pihole-with-a-recursive-dns-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/setting-up-pihole-with-a-recursive-dns-server/</guid>
      <description>Setting up Pi-Hole with a recursive DNS Server This is a project I&amp;rsquo;ve been postponing for about two weeks. In my experience setting up Pi-Hole isn&amp;rsquo;t hard at all but it always ends up taking longer than I expect it to, mainly because I have to track down the sources I used to set it up months ago, so this post will also be for me to later just have it as a reference instead of watching the same video over and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I made my portfolio website</title>
      <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/how-i-made-my-portfolio-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/how-i-made-my-portfolio-website/</guid>
      <description>How I made my portfolio website Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you the process I followed for creating my portfolio website (https://antoniosolismz.com/).
Preparation of the environment First we need to have the machine that our server will run on. In this section I&amp;rsquo;ll show the steps for creating a Virtual Machine that will host our portfolio.
Deploying and configuring the Virtual Machine The cloud service I&amp;rsquo;ll use for my VM is Oracle Cloud since it offers 2 free VM&amp;rsquo;s, and they are enough to run my simple portfolio (The other VM is hosting this blog 😄).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I made my self-hosted WordPress Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/how-i-made-my-wordpress-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.antoniosolismz.com/posts/how-i-made-my-wordpress-blog/</guid>
      <description>How I made my self-hosted WordPress Blog Hello and welcome to my first blog post. In this entry I&amp;rsquo;ll show you the process I followed for creating this blog: a self-hosted WordPress blog in my custom subdomain; and how you can do it for free (excluding the subdomain bit).
Create a VM to host the blog First we need to have the server we&amp;rsquo;ll use to host the blog. I&amp;rsquo;m using Oracle Cloud since (at the time of writing) it offers two VM&amp;rsquo;s (VM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
